Guide to the Collection title
Collection title
1900-1999
XEAT-TEST-001
15 linear_feet 15 boxes
Abstract test. Paragraph test.
Scope and Contents Note
S and C test
Access Note
Collection is open for research.
Arrangement Note
Arrangement test
Acquisition Note
Acq test
Biographical Note
Bio test
Related Materials
Related test
- Miscellaneous, 1900-1972; 10 linear_feet 10 boxes
  Arrangement Note
  Series arrangement note here.
  - Postcard: Native American encampment, approximately 1950-1959 (Box 01, Folder 01)
  - Postcard: Freighting team in front of Arizona Club, 1905 (Box 01, Folder 02)
  - Block and Botkin Gent's Furnishings store, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 03)
  - Las Vegas Town site, approximately 1909-1910 (Box 01, Folder 04)
  - Las Vegas Town site, approximately 1909-1910 (Box 01, Folder 05)
  - Las Vegas, Nevada, 1910 (Box 01, Folder 06)
  - Las Vegas, Nevada, 1910 (Box 01, Folder 07)
  - Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1909-1910 (Box 01, Folder 08)
  - Palace Hotel, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1910 (Box 01, Folder 09)
  - Depot, Clark's Las Vegas Townsite, 1909 (Box 01, Folder 10)
  - Rochela House, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 11)
  - Homes, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1910 (Box 01, Folder 12)
  - Postcard: Block 16, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Cottages, Clark's Las Vegas Townsite, 1911 (Box 01, Folder 14)
  - Postcard: The courthouse, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1930-1934 (Box 01, Folder 15)
  - Dedication of Hermiston Memorial Baptist Church, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1925 March 08 (Box 01, Folder 16)
  - Dedication of Hermiston Memorial Baptist Church, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1925 March 08 (Box 01, Folder 17)
  - Bronze Chief nickel slot machine, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 01, Folder 18)
  - Postcard: Fremont Street, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1931 (Box 01, Folder 19)
  - El Cortez Hotel, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1943-1947 (Box 01, Folder 20)
  - The Frontier Club, 1942 (Box 01, Folder 21)
  - Unidentified man in front of Lady Luck Casino, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 22)
  - City Library, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1943 (Box 01, Folder 23)
  - Postcard: The Pioneer Club and Las Vegas Club, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1950-1959 (Box 01, Folder 24)
  - Racetrack, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1958 June (Box 01, Folder 25)
  - Las Vegas Convention Center, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1958 June (Box 01, Folder 26)
  - 5th street school, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1958 June (Box 01, Folder 27)
  - El Rancho, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1953 (Box 01, Folder 28)
  - Chuckwagon Buffet, El Rancho Vegas, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1953 (Box 01, Folder 29)
  - El Rancho Vegas Casino, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1953 (Box 01, Folder 30)
  - El Rancho, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1953 (Box 01, Folder 31)
  - El Ranch Vegas Cocktail Lounge, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1953 (Box 01, Folder 32)
  - El Rancho, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1953 (Box 01, Folder 33)
  - Water Treatment Facility, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1967-1972 (Box 01, Folder 34)
  - Flooding in Las Vegas, 1970 (Box 01, Folder 35)
  - Flooding in Las Vegas, 1970 (Box 01, Folder 36)
  - Flooding in Las Vegas, 1970 (Box 01, Folder 37)
  - Union Plaza Hotel, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1978 (Box 01, Folder 38)
  - Rose and Palmers, Beatty, NV, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 39)
  - Belmont, Nevada, 1910 (Box 01, Folder 40)
  - Labor Strike, Boulder City, Nevada, 1935 (Box 01, Folder 41)
  - Desert scene, Boulder City, Nevada, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 01, Folder 42)
  - Postcard: United States Mint, Carson City, approximately 1860-1900 (Box 01, Folder 43)
  - Postcard: Bower Mansion, Carson City, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 44)
  - Postcard: Fallon Mercantile Co., Fallon, Nevada, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 01, Folder 45)
  - Postcard: Fallon, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 46)
  - Postcard: Drilling contest, Goldfield, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 47)
  - Postcard: Goldfield Mills, Goldfield, Nevada, approximately 1920-1924 (Box 01, Folder 48)
  - Postcard: Goldfield, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 49)
  - Boulder Canyon, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 50)
  - Start of construction on Hoover Dam, 1931 (Box 01, Folder 51)
  - Hoover Dam, 1933 (Box 01, Folder 52)
  - Hoover Dam construction, 1933 (Box 01, Folder 53)
  - Hoover Dam, 1935 (Box 01, Folder 54)
  - Hoover Dam, 1935 (Box 01, Folder 55)
  - Rhyolite-Goldfield Stage, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 56)
  - Postcard: Rhyolite, Nevada, 1908 (Box 01, Folder 57)
  - Postcard: Prospecting outfit, Rhyolite, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 58)
  - Bottle house, Rhyolite, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 59)
  - Postcard: House in Rhyolite, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 60)
  - Postcard: Miners Union, Rhyolite, Nevada, 1906 (Box 01, Folder 61)
  - Postcard: Washoe Indians, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 62)
  - Ore wagons, 1905 (Box 01, Folder 63)
  - Postcard: A man and burrow-drawn wagon, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 64)
  - Wagon train, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 65)
  - Valley of Fire, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 66)
  - Unidentified equipment, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 67)
  - McGriff Ranch, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 68)
  - Desert wildlife, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 69)
  - Unidentified church, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 70)
  - Nellis Air Force Base, 1940 (Box 01, Folder 71)
  - McCarran Field, 1941 March 15 (Box 01, Folder 72)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 73)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 74)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 75)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 76)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 77)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 78)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 79)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 80)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 81)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 82)
  - Three Kids Mine, Henderson, Nevada, 1972 (Box 01, Folder 83)
  - Unidentified equipment, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 84)
  - Unidentified equipment, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 85)
  - Unidentified equipment, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 86)
  - Postcard: Wild jackalope, approximately 1950-1999 (Box 01, Folder 87)
  - Vue Generale, Monte Carlo, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 88)
  - Hotel de Paris, Monte Carlo, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 89)
  - Casino et Jardins, Nice, France, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 90)
  - Le Theatre Et Terrasses, Monte Carlo, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 01, Folder 91)
  - Amotion picture set, 1930 (Box 01, Folder 92)
- People, 1900-1999; 5 linear_feet 5 boxes
  Note here.
  - Substeries test, 1950-1977; 3 linear_feet 3 boxes
    - Eva Adams, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1977 (Box 02)
    - Eva Adams, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1977 (Box 02)
    - Ellen Albright, approximately 1950-1959 (Box 02)
  - Subseries test, 1924-1999; 3 linear feet 2 boxes
    - Branda Arnold, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1977 (Box 02)
    - Branda Arnold, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1977 (Box 02)
    - Henry J. Bohn, approximately 1940-1969 (Box 02)
    - Lucille Spire Bruner, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 02)
    - Lucille Spire Bruner, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 02)
    - Lucille Spire Bruner, approximately 1950-1999 (Box 02)
    - William Andrews Clark, approximately 1940-1969 (Box 02)
    - Beda Cornwall, 1977 (Box 02)
    - Clarabelle Hanley Decker, 1939 (Box 02)
    - Sam Gay, approximately 1940-1969 (Box 02)
    - Nevada Hatch, Nevada, approximately 1900-1939 (Box 02)
    - Barbara Henry and Hal Erickson, Las Vegas, Nevada, approximately 1977-1978 (Box 02)
    - Julius Jensen, approximately 1950-1999 (Box 02)
    - Tom Kendall, Nevada, approximately 1940-1969 (Box 02)
    - Jack Longstreet, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 02)
    - Reba McKinster, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1952 (Box 02)
    - Elwood Mead, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 02)
    - Elwood Mead, approximately 1940-1969 (Box 02)
    - Paul Mercer, approximately 1950-1999 (Box 02)
    - C. P. Sloan, 1977 (Box 02)
    - Flag pole presentation, 1958 January 07 (Box 02)
    - Southern Nevada Historical Society, 1973 April (Box 02)
    - Group of men, 1977 April 05 (Box 02)
    - Nevada State Senate, Carson City, Nevada, 1977 (Box 02)
    - Winder, Bruno, and Lawson, Nevada, approximately 1940-1969 (Box 02)
    - Goup of individuals, Nevada, approximately 1940-1969 (Box 02)
    - Group of unidentified men, approximately 1900-1949 (Box 02)
    - Men on horseback at Kiel Ranch, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1924 June 30 (Box 02)